sabunta.com 2012-08-30

# Privacy Policy

Sabunta will never spam you or give your personal data to anyone else. You can read our privacy policy detailed below. Don't worry, your private information is safe with us.

We take our customers privacy seriously and we will only collect and use your personal information as outlined below. We shall take all reasonable steps to protect your personal information. For the purpose of this clause, "personal information" shall be defined as detailed in the Promotion of Access to Information Act 2 of 2000 (PAIA).

## Personal information collected

Sabunta does not sell, share or trade customer’s personal information collected online with third parties. 

Personal information collected online will only be disclosed within our corporate group for internal use only. 

## Collection of Personal Information

When you create an account the personal information we collect may include your: 

  * Name and Surname
  * Delivery Address
  * Email Address
  * Telephone Number
  * Mobile Number
  * Date of Birth
  * Gender
  * ID number / passport number; and
  * Non-personal browsing habits and click patterns

The personal information we collect from you will be used in some or all of the following ways: 

  * To deliver the products you have purchased from Sabunta
  * To update you on the delivery of the product and for customer support purposes
  * To provide you with relevant product information 

When you register as a user on Sabunta’s website, we will also use your personal information to send you marketing and/or promotional materials from time to time. You can unsubscribe from marketing information at anytime by using the unsubscribe function within the electronic marketing material. 

## Updating Your Personal Information

You can update your personal information anytime by accessing your account on Sabunta’s website. 

## Security of Your Personal Information

Sabunta ensures that all information collected will be safely and securely stored. 

We protect your personal information by: 

  * Restricting access to personal information
  * Maintaining technology products to prevent unauthorised computer access
  * Securely destroying your personal information when it's no longer needed for our record retention purposes

Sabunta uses 128 - bit SSL (secure sockets layer) encryption technology when processing your financial details. 128-bit SSL encryption is approximated to take at least one trillion years to break, and is the industry standard. 

## Disclosure of Personal Information

We will not share your information with any other organizations other than related companies and those third parties directly related to the delivery of the products you have purchased from Sabunta’s website. 

In exceptional circumstances Sabunta may be required to disclose personal information, such as when there are grounds to believe that the disclosure is necessary to prevent a threat to life or health, or for law enforcement purposes. 

Sabunta is committed to complying with the Promotion of Access to Information Act 2 of 2000 and its principles. 

**If you believe that your privacy has been breached by Sabunta please contact us at contact@sabunta.com and we will resolve the issue.**

## Collection of Computer Data

When you visit Sabunta, our company servers will automatically record information that your browser sends whenever you visit a website. This data may include: 

  * Your computer's IP address
  * Browser type
  * Webpage you were visiting before you came to our site
  * The pages with Sabunta you visit
  * The time spent on those pages, items and information searched for on our site, access times and dates, and other statistics.

This information is collected for analysis and evaluation in order to help us improve our site and the services and products we provide. This data will not be used in association with any other personal information. 

## Changes to the Privacy Policy

Sabunta reserves the right to modify and change the Privacy Policy at any time. Any changes to this policy will be published on our site. 

## Complaints about breaches of privacy

If you are not satisfied with the way in which we handle your enquiry or complaint, please don't hesitate to contact us at contact@sabunta.com
